export const spinningFishing = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: '1. Spinning fishing involves the use of lures.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: '2. Spinning is used only for sea fishing.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'False',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: '3. The reel for spinning is usually mounted under the rod.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: '4. Spinning fishing is ineffective in rivers.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'False',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: '5. Spinning fishing requires constant rod movement.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      '6. Spinning fishing is most popular among anglers targeting predatory fish.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: '7. Spinning can be used without a reel.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'False',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: '8. Spinning fishing does not require casting skills.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'False',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: '9. Spinning allows the use of both live and artificial lures.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: '10. Spinning can be used for fishing from both shore and boat.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
];
